A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office of the Vice President, International Program Review Files FA579
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office of the Vice President, International Program Review Files
1979-1982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA579
1.2 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- William D. Carmichael, I
  - Middle East and Africa Review, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Review, Oct 8, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Middle East and Africa -- New York, 1980 (Box 1)
- Alvin Nelson Puryear, II
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Bangladesh Office, Oct 25, 1980 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- New Delhi, Oct 27, 1980 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Southeast Asia, Oct 30, 1980 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Office of Latin America and the Caribbean -- Budget Documents and Briefing Materials, Oct 1980 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Material re: 1980 Program Review (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Miscellaneous Program Review Information (1/2), 1980 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Miscellaneous Program Review Information (2/2) (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Mexico and Central America Briefing Materials, Oct 1980 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Brazil Program Discussions, Oct 20, 1980 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Developing Country Programs Program Review -- Meetings Schedule, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Meeting Schedule, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- India, Nepal and Sri Lanka, Nov 20, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Bangladesh, Nov 21, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Middle East and North Africa, Dec 3, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Eastern and Southern Africa, Dec 4, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Western and Central Africa, Jan 6, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Mexico and Central America, Nov 6, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Brazil, Nov 7, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Andean Region and the Southern Cone, Nov 10, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Southeast Asia, Nov 16, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Program Review, Dec 18, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Information Papers, 1981 (Box 1)